akashtablet.com 2013-05-15

# 

**Your Privacy** **& our Statement of Intent**

This privacy policy applies to the services available under the domain and subdomains of [www.govasool.com](http://www.govasool.com/) ("GoVasool.com") and applies generally to its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and/or joint venture websites whose specific privacy policies may also be made available on the respective websites. By visiting GoVasool.com, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. GoVasool.com is operated by Emart Solutions India Pvt Ltd.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. At no time will we trade, sell, or distribute organization specific or personal information, including email addresses or other user IDs, to any individual, company, vendor or organization, in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement.

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions at the time of registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the clauses in our Terms and Conditions.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact our customer service at [support@govasool.com](mailto:support@govasool.com) with your comments, questions or concerns.

**Personal Information Collected by GoVasool.com**

When you use GoVasool.com, we collect and store your personal information to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on GoVasool.com. We use this information to internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis and may include the URL that the user came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL the user next went to (whether this URL is on our site or not), the computer browser information, and the user IP address.

Additionally, GoVasool.com collects click-stream data and other preference information on its users in order to improve the design and vendor selection of the site. Click-stream data represents a page-by-page history of a person's site usage.

**How We Use This Personal Information**

GoVasool.com uses this data for the following reasons:

  * \- To provide a point of contact for communicating correspondence including your personal password, technical support and any other reminders, any promotions that you may request on an opt-in basis as a GoVasool.com user

  * \- To assign your user id and password

  * \- To verify your affiliation with the organization using GoVasool.com

  * \- To provide the benefits/services associated with GoVasool.com 

Click-stream data can help determine the popularity of vendors, offers and site features with our audience, allowing us to develop a better site. An individual user's click-stream data is kept in the strictest confidence, and will never be distributed to any party outside of Emart Solutions India Pvt Ltd. 

We use your personal information and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to, among other things, resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; collect payment owed; measure consumer interest in the services provided by us, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms and Conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of these communications using means as described in this policy.

**What Information We Share**

GoVasool.com only shares aggregated data to third party vendors, but it will not disclose information specific to any user or organization, including email address except as described in this privacy policy. To fulfill certain purchases by you, it may be necessary for us to share your information with our partners. Additionally, some participating organizations have requested monthly reports of traffic on GoVasool.com. These reports will reveal only the aggregated viewing habits of GoVasool.com visitors from that organization. The reports will not disclose the user name, login ID or any other personal information of users, including email address.

From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc.

**Service Providers**

GoVasool.com employs third parties to perform specific functions on our behalf. Examples include, without limitation, hosting services, fulfillment, etc. Some providers have access to personal data to provide a service to us, but are bound by agreements with us to not use it for anything other than intended purposes.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. GoVasool.com uses cookies on its site(s) and does link the information stored in cookies to personally identifiable information, including email address, you submit while on the site(s).

GoVasool.com uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate the site(s). A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

Persistent cookies are set to store an encrypted link to your account information, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable GoVasool.com to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on the site(s). If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by our sites and private label sub-domains delivered by GoVasool.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Emails**

GoVasool.com will not send unsolicited emails to registered users without consent. Additionally, users may choose to receive GoVasool.com correspondence, including email reminders of specific vendor offers and GoVasool.com newsletters.

**Opting Out**

All emails sent by GoVasool.com contain directions on how to unsubscribe from future correspondence. In addition, a registered user who wishes that his/her personal information, including email address to be completely removed from the GoVasool.com database should write to us at [support@govasool.com](mailto:support@govasool.com). We will respond to your request within forty five [45] business days. An individual's complete removal of his or her personal information from the database negates that individual's ability to login to GoVasool.com. 

**Notification Of Changes To Privacy Policy**

Users will be notified of changes or revisions to this privacy policy, including our email practices, by a notice posted on GoVasool.com. The notice will contain a link, whereby the Privacy policy can be examined in full. It is advisable therefore to check our Web site frequently to see recent changes in the policy. As always, a user who is not amenable to the conditions of a revised privacy policy may opt out of using GoVasool.com, by means outlined earlier in this document.

**Agents**

GoVasool.com may use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders and a payment card processing company to accept your payments. In some cases, online purchases facilitated by the GoVasool.com portal are subject to the privacy policies of the participating businesses or Websites where such transactions are conducted.

On GoVasool.com, you will be required to submit the following information to transact:

  * \- First Name and Last Name

  * \- Shipping or billing address or both

  * \- Mobile/Phone number

  * \- Email address

In all cases, any transaction conducted through GoVasool.com is secured and encrypted with SSL technology and certified.

**Limits**

Although your privacy is of paramount concern to us, GoVasool.com cannot suppress information where the withholding of such information represents a violation of Indian laws or is needed by relevant government agencies. GoVasool.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information, including email address, as required by law or such competent authority and when it is believed that disclosure is necessary to protect GoVasool.com's rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Emart Solutions India Pvt Ltd.

As a User, you expressly agree to refrain from doing, either personally or through a third party, any of the following:

  * \- Granting or permitting others access to GoVasool.com by using your name or password

  * \- Duplicating and sharing of any material and content made available from your access to GoVasool.com

  * \- Copying and modifying, publishing or redistributing any content available from and on GoVasool.com

  * \- Engaging in any conduct that violates the Copyright Act and/or other laws of India.

  * \- Attempting to disrupt or violate the security of GoVasool.com

**Your Consent**

As a user of GoVasool.com, you consent to our collection and storage of your personal information, including email address, (as defined above) in our database, and to our use of aggregated and non-personal information generated by the viewing habits of our users.
